<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wizards of Java on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m5-fun-with-programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wizards of Java on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m5-fun-with-programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m5-fun-with-programming/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m5-fun-with-programming/features/</guid>
      <description>General This e-learning unit is designed for English-speaking first-semester students enrolled in a media and computing program. It teaches the fundamentals of Java programming in a creative and engaging way. Instead of traditional, dry exercises, students are guided through a magical storyline where programming concepts are explained using potions, magical capes, wands, and other fantasy elements. To ensure long-term usability, all learning content is managed via a connected headless CMS, allowing professors and students to adapt and expand the platform beyond the semester.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m5-fun-with-programming/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m5-fun-with-programming/process/</guid>
      <description>Background &amp;amp; Starting Point This project builds on the insights we gained in the ‘Didactics of Media’ course with Prof. Weber-Wulff last semester. In that course, we explored different ways of conveying knowledge to learners. We also examined what learning actually means and how many different approaches there are to understanding a subject.&#xA;At the end of the semester, we worked in small groups to design e-learning unit concepts based on selected topics from the Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s course Informatics 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tools</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m5-fun-with-programming/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m5-fun-with-programming/tools/</guid>
      <description>Concept &amp;amp; Design Miro was used for the initial brainstorming sessions, for finalizing the requirements and the concept. We used it as well for the first low-fidelity prototypes. It allowed the team to discuss and visualize ideas and record decisions. Figma was used to create the UI component library, style guide, and final design for the user interface of the application. Frontend Development Nuxt.js is a powerful Vue.js framework that simplifies the development of web applications by providing a nice-to-handle directory structure, server-side rendering, routing functionalities, and other built-in features.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
