<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MakeSign on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b2-makesign/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MakeSign on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b2-makesign/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b2-makesign/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b2-makesign/features/</guid>
      <description>Features Using Makesign, you can project your own pictures, posters and GIFs on a screen and manage your content with an easy-to-use interface at any time. Create slideshows, choosing how long each of the images are being displayed. For dynamic displays, such as the dashboard, where you can see what tool is booked for how long, you can simply create a website and connect it with the system. The projection runs via a Raspberry Pi, which means you can connect them to basically any screen you have lying around and give them a new life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b2-makesign/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b2-makesign/process/</guid>
      <description>Process At the beginning of the project, we had a kick-off meeting with Prof. Dr. Barne, our project supervisor, and Martin Holzhauer, our lead connection to the IDiA Makerspace. Martin explained his needs for the digital signage, which considers showing ads for the Makerspace and most importantly, the booking reservations of the IDiA booking website. To get a general idea on digital signage, we looked around the campus for already existing digital signage use cases for inspiration, as well as possible cases, in which it might be practical to implement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b2-makesign/techstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b2-makesign/techstack/</guid>
      <description> Communication Zoom Whatsapp Signal Discord Organization Github Google-Docs Programming Bootstrap Javascript Ruby on Rails Rubymine Shell Ubuntu Visual Studio Code CSS Design Figma Utility Docker </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
