<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PAM on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b5-pam/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PAM on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b5-pam/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b5-pam/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b5-pam/process/</guid>
      <description>Process The Project was both a technologically tricky undertaking, and a means for us to learn how programming projects will work in the future, with a large focus on Agile Development and SCRUM-style Progress management. We started by setting up a regular Scrum Schedule. Sprints were undertaken on a bi-weekly basis, with remote progress meetings every second week between the sprints, regularly on Wednesdays. We started off by examining the original site, and taking a look at the programming language that had been chosen for us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b5-pam/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b5-pam/features/</guid>
      <description>Features Completely Updated Codebase The original PAM was written in Springboot/Vaadin. The new PAM is written in React/Typescript, with usage of Figma for the design amongst other tools. Of course, this meant re-working the Tool from the ground-up in order to get all the old features working, before adding new features down the line. *&#xA;New Design The original PAM was not as appealing to the eye as it could be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b5-pam/techstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b5-pam/techstack/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack We used the following technologies in our Project: Future As this is a project on a limited-time basis, we are not planning on adding new features. However, we are going to add enough comments and documentation so that the next group to pick it up and try to improve on it will have an easier time. Future improvements to PAM would include Syntax Investigation of the diagrams, more in-depth filtering, perhaps even a social media share function.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
