<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Moodle Plugin on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m4-moodle-plugin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Moodle Plugin on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m4-moodle-plugin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project Architecture</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m4-moodle-plugin/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m4-moodle-plugin/architecture/</guid>
      <description>Overview Moodle System Architecture Plugins must follow Moodle’s technical and organisational guidelines to qualify for the official plugin directory. Moodle consists of its core with different subsystems and a substantial amount of plugins. These plugins need to be of a specific type. For our plugins these are quiz report and question behaviour. A clear type assignment is essential, because plugins without an unambiguous type cannot be correctly installed or published.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenges</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m4-moodle-plugin/challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m4-moodle-plugin/challenges/</guid>
      <description>Moodle&amp;#39;s Documentation In the early stages of the project we found that Moodle’s official plugin documentation was incomplete and occasionally outdated. This issue complicated our analysis of the platform architecture and the placement of our own plugins. Due to challenges encountered with the documentation, a non-standard plugin was found that delivered some of the intended features later in the project. This strategic realignment involved revising the schedule and re-engineering the solution around these proven capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m4-moodle-plugin/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m4-moodle-plugin/features/</guid>
      <description>General Teachers can choose to enable student reviews for their tests. Installing the plugins does not mean they will be used for every test. Teachers can turn the feature on and off for each test they create. If this feature is activated, students will be asked to rate the difficulty of a varying number of questions. The review will be displayed at the end of the question and consists of a heatbar with review options from easy to very difficult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m4-moodle-plugin/techstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m4-moodle-plugin/techstack/</guid>
      <description> Organization Gitlab for code collaboration and distribution Miro for brainstorming and graphics Figma for visualization prototyping Discord for internal project discussions Zoom for weekly updates with stakeholders Plugin Moodle development environment:&#xA;PHP 8 Apache 2 PostgreSQL 15 Debian 12 Plugin development:&#xA;PHP 8 Mustache CSS JavaScript Testing Microsoft Playwright for End-to-End-Tests Docker for Gitlab CI Nodejs for local execution </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m4-moodle-plugin/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss25/master/m4-moodle-plugin/future/</guid>
      <description>Starting Point The project was designed to be used in the upcoming semester by our supervisor Prof. Dr. Lucy Weggler. The creation of this plugin was based on her lacking a reliable difficulty label for her large number of math test questions. To generate difficulty labels before this project, she developed a pipeline that extracts key concepts from math questions using a language model, based on the assumption that more concepts indicate higher difficulty.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
