<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>John the Explorer on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws24/bachelor/b4-john-the-explorer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in John the Explorer on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws24/bachelor/b4-john-the-explorer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws24/bachelor/b4-john-the-explorer/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws24/bachelor/b4-john-the-explorer/features/</guid>
      <description>Personalized Travel Planning Discover affordable flights, personalized hotel recommendations, and real-time availability based on your preferences, budget, and location. Get tailored activity ideas and packing suggestions, all while integrating weather conditions at your destination. Interactive Travel Insights Explore activities, landmarks, and local events in your chosen city, with insights on hidden gems and local favorites. Receive detailed flight schedules, durations and prices. AI-Driven Dynamic Assistance Engage with an AI-powered NPC for conversational trip planning, enjoy a hands-free experience through speech recognition and text-to-speech technologies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws24/bachelor/b4-john-the-explorer/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws24/bachelor/b4-john-the-explorer/process/</guid>
      <description>Conceptualization &amp;amp; Design The project began with brainstorming sessions, where we explored various ideas, including NPC-based games and AI assistants. After gathering insights from online resources and real-world applications, we decided to merge AI with an immersive travel experience. In the Requirement Analysis phase, we defined the user needs and project goals, ensuring that the platform would offer personalized travel recommendations and seamless interaction. Moving to Design and Prototyping, we created system architecture and UI designs that would provide users with a smooth and intuitive experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws24/bachelor/b4-john-the-explorer/techstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws24/bachelor/b4-john-the-explorer/techstack/</guid>
      <description>Core Components Unity: For developing the interactive NPC interface and integrating all features.&#xA;Amadeus API: Used to fetch real-time flight and hotel data.&#xA;Gemini API: It is responsible for answering user queries.&#xA;Vosk Speech Recognition: It is used to convert user speech into text.&#xA;Pixabay API: For fetching images based on keywords such as city or country names.&#xA;Python TTS: It delivers audio responses to user queries.&#xA;Programming Languages C#: For implementing the Unity-based interface and interaction logic.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
