<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aquasolace on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m1-gaming-for-future/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aquasolace on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m1-gaming-for-future/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m1-gaming-for-future/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m1-gaming-for-future/process/</guid>
      <description>Initial Meetings The three of us, who had worked on the simulation last semester, provided the new team members with a brief introduction to the codebase and detailed information about water scarcity, our algorithms, and other essential aspects. Communication and Iteration We held weekly Scrum meetings with product owners to iterate on and refine project details, working in sprints to ensure continuous progress and alignment with our goals. Programming Workflow We managed our Source Code using the Gitflow Workflow and GitLab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m1-gaming-for-future/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m1-gaming-for-future/features/</guid>
      <description>Features Supervised tile based gridmap interactions Map interactions are controlled and supervised in order to restrict specific player interactions, removing some of the previous sandbox-aspect of the game.&#xA;Ground water level sensitive game winning conditions Player actions directly influence groundwater levels. These influence changes are computed by respecting a data-table though and built to try and mimic somereal-life behavior in the environment.&#xA;Reviving species Such objectives are displayed in the form of quests and can be achieved in the game by modifying the biomes configuration on the map and applying the right configurations and some other hidden conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m1-gaming-for-future/techstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m1-gaming-for-future/techstack/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack Overview Our project utilizes a diverse tech stack to support various aspects of development, design, 3D modeling, music production, and communication.&#xA;Development: We leverage Unity Engine for robust game development, integrated seamlessly with JetBrains Rider and Visual Studio for efficient coding and version control through GitLab.&#xA;Design: Graphic and UI design is powered by industry-standard tools including Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator, along with collaborative platforms like Figma and Mural for design iterations and team collaboration.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
