<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>External Stakeholder on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/categories/external-stakeholder/</link>
    <description>Recent content in External Stakeholder on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/categories/external-stakeholder/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Capsearch</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m5-capsearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m5-capsearch/</guid>
      <description>In large-scale companies with numerous employees, identifying the ideal project that fosters professional growth and aligns perfectly with individual expectations has consistently posed a challenge. Even after discovering a suitable project, the conventional back-and-forth email exchanges for sharing general information can prove time consuming and labor intensive for both employees and managers. Our Goal CapSearch offers an innovative solution to this challenge. By digitizing the process, Capsearch streamlines how employees are paired with projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CogniCity</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m3-cognicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m3-cognicity/</guid>
      <description>The Problem How good our cognitive abilities are has a significant impact on how good we perceive our own life quality.1&#xA;Unfortunately some health conditions and their treatments can lead to a decline in these abilities. For example, imagine a teenager who has to spend a lot of time in the hospital due to a chronic illness and is unable to attend school regularly. Or a young adult who suffers from a heart disease and has to take regular medication which can affect their cognitive abilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LunarFit</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b3-lunarfit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b3-lunarfit/</guid>
      <description>Our Goal Approximately 85% of women experience menstrual-related complaints. Even though it commonly interferes with everyday life, the menstrual cycle is often ignored or even tabooed. Especially in sports, learning about their cycle, helps athletes mitigate complaints. Adapting the training accordingly allows them to harness long-term performance benefits. Education and awareness are crucial to end stigmatization and empower female athletes. Features Lunarfit aims to bridge the gap between menstrual health and athletic performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OrgXtract</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m4-orgxtract/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m4-orgxtract/</guid>
      <description>Our Goal The project aims to transform organizational charts, traditionally stored as PDFs, into a machine-readable format to enhance transparency in German authorities personnel structure. It focuses on converting these static documents into data that can be easily analyzed, to provide deeper insights into public administration. The goal was to create a tool for the Open Knowledge Foundation team to extract data from organizational charts of public authorities in PDF and use the output data to conduct their research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAM</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b5-pam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b5-pam/</guid>
      <description>Background The Tool&amp;rsquo;s purpose is to allow for the simple creation of Process Diagrams using a simple interface, as well the saving and exporting of those diagrams in various formats as required, organizing them depending on the preferences of the creators by allowing for a custom repository structure of folders and sub-folders. It also has an internal organization scheme following a simple folder/file format. However, it was rather simple, focusing on the basic features initially.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
