<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SEMPY on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b4-sempy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SEMPY on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b4-sempy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b4-sempy/techstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b4-sempy/techstack/</guid>
      <description> Projektmanagement Miro Github Discord Whatsapp Design / Styling CSS Bootstrap Miro HTML Chromeextension JavaScript Backend Python OpenAI API YouTubeAPI Flask </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b4-sempy/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b4-sempy/features/</guid>
      <description>Features Our SEMPY Button offers a relaxed shopping experience that provides customers with recommendations based on the information from the three major platforms: idealo, Amazon, and YouTube. Whether the customer is interested in products like a &amp;ldquo;Victorinox Huntsman&amp;rdquo;, an &amp;ldquo;MSR Hubba Hubba 2 NX&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;Apple AirPods 3&amp;rdquo;, the SEMPY-AI Tool caters to the customer&amp;rsquo;s individual needs.&#xA;Screenshot of SEMPY-modal on the idealo Website. We take information from idealo, YouTube and Amazon and give them to the OpenAi to process and summarize them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b4-sempy/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b4-sempy/process/</guid>
      <description>Process Pipeline of data processing. At the beginning of the project, there was a brainstorming phase where we wanted to define how our project should look like at the end of the semester. Initially, we thought of having a tool where customers could have a conversation on the idealo website and ask everything about the product. We took inspiration from Perplexity AI, ChatGPT, and similar AI tools.&#xA;After a long discussion, we concluded that we would generate the output of the OpenAI API and place it on the website.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
