<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Technology on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/study_focus/web-technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web Technology on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/study_focus/web-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Capsearch: Bridging Talent and Career</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m5-capsearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/master/m5-capsearch/</guid>
      <description>In large-scale companies with numerous employees, identifying the ideal project that fosters professional growth and aligns perfectly with individual expectations has consistently posed a challenge. Even after discovering a suitable project, the conventional back-and-forth email exchanges for sharing general information can prove time consuming and labor intensive for both employees and managers. Our Goal CapSearch offers an innovative solution to this challenge. By digitizing the process, Capsearch streamlines how employees are paired with projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LunarFit</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b3-lunarfit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b3-lunarfit/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Makesign</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b2-makesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b2-makesign/</guid>
      <description>Our Goal Plakate in den Gebäuden der Universität sind meist veraltet, da es sehr mühsam und zeitaufwendig ist, neue aufzuhängen und die alten zu entsorgen. Unsere Idee ist es, Digital Signage zu verwenden, um alten Bildschirmen als Anzeigetafeln ein neues Leben auf den Campus zu ermöglichen, um so eine einfache und effiziente Möglichkeit zu bieten Webpage-Poster oder Videos zur Schau zu stellen. Hierfür entwickeln wir Open Source Technologien weiter und nutzen günstige Raspberry Pi(Mini Computer), um in Verbindung mit alten Monitoren eine Möglichkeit für ein Signage Netzwerk bieten, welches alten Monitoren wieder eine Funktion gibt und jeglichen Organisatoren an dem Campus die Vermarktung von Veranstaltungen erleichtert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAM</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b5-pam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b5-pam/</guid>
      <description>Background The Tool&amp;rsquo;s purpose is to allow for the simple creation of Process Diagrams using a simple interface, as well the saving and exporting of those diagrams in various formats as required, organizing them depending on the preferences of the creators by allowing for a custom repository structure of folders and sub-folders. It also has an internal organization scheme following a simple folder/file format. However, it was rather simple, focusing on the basic features initially.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sempy</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b4-sempy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b4-sempy/</guid>
      <description>Our Goal The goal of this project is to offer an AI driven research agent on idealo&amp;rsquo;s price comparison platform that supports users who have not yet made a decision on which product to buy and are looking for additional information. The team The SEMPY team consists of 5 young IMI students that came together to build this project. Through this project, we were able to gain a lot of knowledge about working with AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Title</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b0-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ss24/bachelor/b0-example/</guid>
      <description>Text outside of sections: As the abstract is shown before the content as it&amp;rsquo;s own section, you should use the &amp;ldquo;intro&amp;rdquo; top matter now if you want to have some extra text before the sections.&#xA;Section Title Section Text Tick Trick Track </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
