<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Technology on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/study_focus/web-technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web Technology on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/study_focus/web-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Elara Health</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws24/bachelor/b6-elara-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws24/bachelor/b6-elara-health/</guid>
      <description>Our Goal ME/CFS (Myalgische Enzephalomyelitis/Chronic Fatigue Syndrome) affects millions of people worldwide, yet it remains poorly understood and often stigmatized.&#xA;Elara aims to bridge this gap by empowering patients with tools to better understand their condition, track their symptoms, and access personalized health insights. By fostering awareness and providing actionable recommendations, Elara supports ME/CFS patients in managing their daily lives more effectively.&#xA;Therefore, we want to build a website for Elara to help it reach out to people and provide them with the resources they need to navigate life with ME/CFS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helm sucht Kopf</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws24/bachelor/b3-helm-sucht-kopf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws24/bachelor/b3-helm-sucht-kopf/</guid>
      <description> The Goal The goal of #HelmSuchtKopf is to inspire and attract more trainees to the fire department.Through our website&amp;rsquo;s interactive features, we aim to make the process enjoyable, interactive and engaging, helping tomorrow’s heroes find the entry opportunities that best match their aspirations. Christoph Friedrich Duha Kasem Maria Ivanova Nam Khanh Nguyen Phuong Nhi Phan Sandip Sarraf Sara Tahmasebi Adar </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoiSum</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws24/bachelor/b2-voisum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws24/bachelor/b2-voisum/</guid>
      <description>Our Goal In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, we&amp;rsquo;re aiming to transform how people consume voice messages by creating an AI-powered solution that cuts through the noise. Our tool takes those rambling voice notes and delivers just the essential content - no fluff, no filler words, just the key points you need. By combining speech-to-text, smart summarization, and voice synthesis, we&amp;rsquo;re not just saving time - we&amp;rsquo;re making voice communication more efficient while keeping it personal.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
