<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PlapperDu on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws25/bachelor/b1-sprachentwicklungsapp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PlapperDu on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws25/bachelor/b1-sprachentwicklungsapp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws25/bachelor/b1-sprachentwicklungsapp/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws25/bachelor/b1-sprachentwicklungsapp/development/</guid>
      <description>Process PlapperDu began with enthusiastic brainstorming and a flood of concepts. In the early stages, an extensive list of features was gathered, and the team familiarized themselves with the tools and frameworks required for implementation.&#xA;However, the first major challenge soon emerged: defining the scope. With so many possibilities, it was difficult to pinpoint exactly what was essential and what was out of reach.&#xA;Initially, the goal was to map out everything perfectly from the start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws25/bachelor/b1-sprachentwicklungsapp/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws25/bachelor/b1-sprachentwicklungsapp/features/</guid>
      <description>Features Dashboard&#xA;Get a quick overview of your ongoing learning modules or weekly challenge, open language assessments and daily activities.&#xA;Milestones and Badges: Capture and celebrate every important step in your and your child&amp;rsquo;s language development journey with Milestones and Badges.&#xA;Learning Modules&#xA;Access short, interactive lessons that teach you how to support language learning in your everyday life.&#xA;Progress&#xA;Vocabulary Tracker: Track every new word or sentence your child learns and watch their personal digital dictionary grow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tools</title>
      <link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws25/bachelor/b1-sprachentwicklungsapp/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ws25/bachelor/b1-sprachentwicklungsapp/tools/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack Django We used Django as our server-side framework for managing core business logic, secure user authentication and ensuring reliable data persistence.&#xA;Vue.js For the frontend development, we utilized Vue.js to implement a reactive and interactive user interface.&#xA;Nuxt.js Nuxt is a framework built on top of Vue.js. It provides built-in features such as automatic routing and server-side rendering (SSR), which allowed us to create a more efficient and seamless frontend.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
